{
    "irrelevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.25 LTS (October 15, 2024; 5 months ago) [\u00b1] 21.0.5 LTS (",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.0.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.0,2021,\"Introduced record classes, pattern matching, and sealed classes for enhanced data modelling abilities\"",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "irrelevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.25 LTS (October\u00a015, 2024; 5 months ago[3]) [\u00b1] 21.0.5 L",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9. 23.0,2024,",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 7.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.5 years.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 7.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.0.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.9, released on July 10, 2018.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.13 (LTS), released on February 11, 2025.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is 4.8.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.32 (LTS),\"December 13, 2022\",\"December 13, 2022\",3 years",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is 4.8.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.13,\"May 14, 2019\",\"June 27, 2019\",2.5 years",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9, which was released in November 2024.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.5 years.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.0, which was released on September 23, 2019.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.NET Framework\u2014and released source code for the .NET Core CoreCLR implementation, source for the \"entire [...] library stack\" for .NET Core, and announced",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9, released in November 2024.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.32 (LTS),\"December 13, 2022\",\"December 13, 2022\",3 years",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.NET Core, and announced the adoption of a conventional (\"bazaar\"-like) open-source development model under the stewardship of the .NET Foundation.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.NET Core web apps, command-line/console apps, libraries and Universal Windows Platform apps. Prior to .NET Core 3.0, it did not implement Windows Form",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.0.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.0, released in November 2024.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        }
    ]
}